https://www.robabdul.com/privacy-policy/

RobAbdul.com is committed to privacy
RobAbdul.com is committed to privacy. I am committed to protecting the privacy of those using my site and the confidentiality of the personal information with which my subscribers provide.
Your personal information is safe with RobAbdul.com. RobAbdul.com will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties.
At RobAbdul.com I use the information I collect to serve my customers in the following ways:
If you contact me via my website, I will reply to you with the email address and the address my email reply to the name you provided whilst completing the online form on my contact page.
If you become a subscriber to the RobAbdul.com website or use other services your name, e-mail address, address and other information on the subscription form are kept by me and used alert you to new products and or services of which you may be interested in.
I may also use your contact information to let you know about enhancements to the site and your subscription entitlements.
If you would rather not receive this information please inform my by e-mail at privacy at robabdul.com.
Google Analytics
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilises the data collected to track and examine the use of www.robabdul.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.
Google may use the data collected to contextualise and personalise the ads of its own advertising network.
Personal data collected: Cookie and Usage Data. Place of processing: USA. Find Google’s privacy policy here.
Third party
I use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit my website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
Further Information
For further information on data protection and privacy contact:-
Information on the protection act 1998 is also on the data protection Commissioner’s web site at www.dataprotection.gov.uk or www.dpr.gov.uk
Use of this site is subject to our terms and conditions.
Translate »
